<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Index on Financial Advice</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/</link><description>Recent content in Index on Financial Advice</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zhade.dev/financial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Certificate of Deposit</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/certificate-of-deposit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/certificate-of-deposit/</guid><description>Certificate of Deposit # Yield Liquidity Low Low TLDR: A certificate of deposit is a great way to lock in higher interest rates than a normal savings account for a liquidity penalty.
A certificate of deposit (CD) is a type of savings vessel where a bank guarantees a higher interest rate in exchange for your agreement not to withdraw the money for some fixed period.</description></item><item><title>Cryptocurrency</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/crypto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/crypto/</guid><description>Cryptocurrency # TLDR: Cryptocurrency is an extremely speculative investment that is good to round out your investment portfolio. This type of investment requires the highest risk tolerance, and as such should be integrated into your portfolio wisely.</description></item><item><title>High Yield Savings Account</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/high-yield-savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/high-yield-savings/</guid><description>High Yield Savings Account # Yield Liquidity Lowest Extremely High TLDR: High yield savings accounts are an OK way to hold onto cash for the future. While the yield is lower than storing in other places, this kind of account guarantees liquidity for your money.
A high yield savings account is a savings account by a bank that is designed to give you a higher yield than other savings accounts.</description></item><item><title>Real Estate</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/real-estate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/real-estate/</guid><description>Real Estate # TLDR: Real estate is a fantastic investment if you have a large amount of money to invest. While it has lower liquidity, it provides a passive revenue stream through rent, and also tends to appreciate over time in absolute value making it a very safe investment.</description></item><item><title>Savings Bonds</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/savings-bonds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/savings-bonds/</guid><description>Savings Bonds # Yield Liquidity Medium Low TLDR: Savings bonds are an excellent way to save money, as long as don&amp;rsquo;t need the money for some time. Their yield far outpaces other financial tools for saving money, including High Yield Savings Accounts, while also having basically no risk.
A bond is an IOU issued by the government (or some other entity) to a lender (you).</description></item><item><title>Stocks</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/stocks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/stocks/</guid><description>Stocks # TLDR: Stocks are the ideal choice for investing if you have a medium risk tolerance and a lesser amount of money to invest. Many investment vessels, such as IRAs and 401ks are optimized for stock investments.
Stocks represent ownership of a fraction of a company. This means that changes that affect the value of the company (such as a good quarter of sales) are also reflected in the stock price.</description></item></channel></rss>