<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Index on Financial Advice</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/</link><description>Recent content in Index on Financial Advice</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zhade.dev/financial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bonds</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/bonds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/bonds/</guid><description>Bonds # TLDR: Bonds (especially Treasury Inflation Bonds) are an excellent way to save money, if you know that you will not need the money for some time. Their yield far outpaces other financial tools for saving money, including High Yield Savings Accounts.
Bonds are commonly known as a &amp;ldquo;boring&amp;rdquo; investment due to being guaranteed, low interest money. However, if one looks at bonds as a savings vessel instead of an investment one, the value proposition is a lot better.</description></item><item><title>Cryptocurrency</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/crypto/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/crypto/</guid><description>Cryptocurrency # TLDR: Cryptocurrency is an extremely speculative investment that is good to round out your investment portfolio. This type of investment requires the highest risk tolerance, and as such should be integrated into your portfolio wisely.</description></item><item><title>High Yield Savings Account</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/high-yield-savings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/high-yield-savings/</guid><description>High Yield Savings Account # TLDR: High yield savings accounts are an OK way to hold onto cash for the future. While the yield is lower than storing in other places, this kind of account guarantees liquidity for your money.</description></item><item><title>Real Estate</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/real-estate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/real-estate/</guid><description>Real Estate # TLDR: Real estate is a fantastic investment if you have a large amount of money to invest. While it has lower liquidity, it provides a passive revenue stream through rent, and also tends to appreciate over time in absolute value making it a very safe investment.</description></item><item><title>Stocks</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/stocks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/investments/stocks/</guid><description>Stocks # TLDR: Stocks are the ideal choice for investing if you have a medium risk tolerance and a lesser amount of money to invest. Many investment vessels, such as IRAs and 401ks are optimized for stock investments.</description></item><item><title>Financial Calculator</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/tools/calculator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/tools/calculator/</guid><description>Financial Calculator # Coming soon! This page will have a calculator that will help you calculate a model for your financial goals.</description></item></channel></rss>