<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Savings on Financial Advice</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/</link><description>Recent content in Savings on Financial Advice</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Certificate of Deposit</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/certificate-of-deposit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/certificate-of-deposit/</guid><description>Certificate of Deposit # Yield Liquidity Low Low TLDR: A certificate of deposit is a great way to lock in higher interest rates than a normal savings account for a liquidity penalty.
A certificate of deposit (CD) is a type of savings vessel where a bank guarantees a higher interest rate in exchange for your agreement not to withdraw the money for some fixed period.</description></item><item><title>High Yield Savings Account</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/high-yield-savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/high-yield-savings/</guid><description>High Yield Savings Account # Yield Liquidity Lowest Extremely High TLDR: High yield savings accounts are an OK way to hold onto cash for the future. While the yield is lower than storing in other places, this kind of account guarantees liquidity for your money.
A high yield savings account is a savings account by a bank that is designed to give you a higher yield than other savings accounts.</description></item><item><title>Savings Bonds</title><link>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/savings-bonds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/financial/savings/savings-bonds/</guid><description>Savings Bonds # Yield Liquidity Medium Low TLDR: Savings bonds are an excellent way to save money, as long as don&amp;rsquo;t need the money for some time. Their yield far outpaces other financial tools for saving money, including High Yield Savings Accounts, while also having basically no risk.
A bond is an IOU issued by the government (or some other entity) to a lender (you).</description></item></channel></rss>